

Stefania Rosca

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

stefi.codes

P Barcelona, Spain

642-129-550

stefania.rosca2309@gmail.com

Frontend developer working with React. In addition to programming, I have over five years of experience in Digital Marketing and Communication at top 500 companies.

Awarded a scholarship to participate at the Recurse Center in New York City.

Invited to speak at <u>QueerJS</u> in Paris about "The importance of community when transitioning to tech" and will be talking about testing at the <u>codebar Festival</u>.

<u>CURRENT PROJECT:</u> Building an <u>app (see code)</u> to connect skiers and snowboarders who live close to a specific resort to pair up for a few ski/snowboard adventures. More projects on my <u>portfolio</u>.

SKILLS: JavaScript(ES6+), React, TypeScript, Unit Testing with Jest and the React Testing Library, HTML, CSS(BEM naming convention and SAAS), Git, Bootstrap, Node, Express, MySQL.

EXPERIENCE

Geneva Business School

Associate Professor

Teaching Introduction to Coding

SEPTEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

- Design and development of course syllabi, learning activities, and resources.
- Assessing student learning achievements and offering student support time.
- Organizing a panel for the students where professionals share what it is like working in a tech role

Criteo

JUNE 2020 - DECEMBER 2020

Technical Solutions Engineer

Responsible for the technical integration and design of Criteo's online advertising products for the Middle East market.

- Code assistance, troubleshooting in JavaScript and tags/Pixel implementation on client's websites.
- Product feeds setup and debugging in XML
- Solve client problems using a variety of analytical and technical tools including traffic analysis, querying databases (SQL), and troubleshooting client-side code.

The Recurse Center

APRIL 2020 - JUNE 2020

Participant

The Recurse Center is a self-directed, community-driven educational retreat for programmers in New York City intended for people who want to get dramatically better at programming.

Softonic Social Media Manager MAY 2017 - OCTOBER 2019

Bitdefender

Social Media Manager

NOVEMBER 2015 - MAY 2017

IBM

DECEMBER 2013 - NOVEMBER 2015

Social Media and Digital Strategist — April 2015 - November 2015 Marketing Campaign Specialist — December 2013 - April 2015

Hewlett Packard

FEBRUARY 2013 - DECEMBER 2013

Contract administrator

Oracle

SEPTEMBER 2011 - JUNE 2012

Service Renewal Representative — March 2012 – June 2012 Customer Reference Specialist D/A/CH & Nordics — September 2011 - March 2012

Hewlett Packard

FEBRUARY 2010 - SEPTEMBER 2011

Special Pricing Specialist (Smart Quote Team)

EDUCATION

CodeOp - Product Management Course

CodeOp - Full-Stack Development Course

freeCodeCamp - JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

CS50's Introduction to Computer Science Course – "Harvard University" – offered online via EdX

freeCodeCamp - Responsive Web Design Certification

Master's Degree - Business Administration (in German) - "Academy of Economic Studies"

Bachelor's Degree - Business Administration (in German) - "Academy of Economic Studies"

Erasmus Student Grant – Business Administration – "University of Applied Sciences Munich"

LANGUAGES

English – fluent German – advanced Spanish – intermediate